<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Information Book</string>

    <string name="united_kingdom">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: London \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: London \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: English \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 242,495 km^2 \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: GBP \n\n

        \t\t The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, commonly known as the United Kingdom (UK) or Britain,is a country in Northwestern Europe, off the north-western coast of the continental mainland. It comprises England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland.[j][18] It includes the island of Great Britain, the north-eastern part of the island of Ireland, and most of the smaller islands within the British Isles.[19] Northern Ireland shares a land border with the Republic of Ireland; otherwise, the United Kingdom is surrounded by the Atlantic Ocean, the North Sea, the English Channel, the Celtic Sea, and the Irish Sea. The total area of the United Kingdom is 94,060 square miles (243,610 km2),[20][21] with an estimated 2022 population of nearly 67 million people.

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom has evolved from a series of annexations, unions and separations of constituent countries over several hundred years. The Treaty of Union between the Kingdom of England (which included Wales) and the Kingdom of Scotland in 1707 resulted in their unification to become the Kingdom of Great Britain. Its union in 1801 with the Kingdom of Ireland created the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland. Most of Ireland seceded from the UK in 1922, leaving the present United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, which formally adopted its name in 1927.[k] The nearby Isle of Man, Guernsey and Jersey are not part of the UK, being Crown Dependencies, but the British government is responsible for their defence and international representation.[22]

\n\n\t\t The UK became the first industrialised country and was the world\'s foremost power for the majority of the 19th and early 20th centuries, particularly during the \"Pax Britannica\" between 1815 and 1914.[23][24] The British Empire, at its height in the 1920s, encompassed almost a quarter of the world\'s landmass and population, and was the largest empire in history; however, its involvement in the First World War and the Second World War damaged Britain\'s economic power and a global wave of decolonisation led to the independence of most British colonies.[25][26][27] British influence can be observed in the legal and political systems of many of its former colonies, and the UK\'s culture remains globally influential, particularly in literature, language, music and sport. English is the world\'s most widely spoken language and the third-most spoken native language.[28]

\n\n\t\t The United Kingdom is a constitutional monarchy and parliamentary democracy. The capital and largest city of the United Kingdom (as well as the capital of England) is London. The cities of Edinburgh, Cardiff, and Belfast are respectively the national capitals of Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. Other major cities include Birmingham, Manchester, Glasgow, and Leeds.[31] The UK consists of three distinct legal jurisdictions: England and Wales, Scotland, and Northern Ireland. This is due to these areas retaining their existing legal systems even after joining the UK.[32] Since 1998, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland also have their own devolved governments and legislatures, each with varying powers.[33]

\n\n\t\t The UK has the world\'s sixth-largest economy by nominal gross domestic product (GDP), and the ninth-largest by purchasing power parity. It is a recognised nuclear state and is ranked fourth globally in military expenditure.[34][35] The UK has been a permanent member of the UN Security Council since its first session in 1946. It is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations, the Council of Europe, the G7, the OECD, NATO, the Five Eyes, AUKUS and the CPTPP.
    </string>

    <string name="france">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Paris \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Paris \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: French \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 643,801 km^2 \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro \n\n

        \t\tFrance (French: [fʁɑ̃s] ⓘ), officially the French Republic (French: République française [ʁepyblik fʁɑ̃sɛːz]),[14] is a country located primarily in Western Europe. It also includes overseas regions and territories in the Americas and the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans,[XII] giving it one of the largest discontiguous exclusive economic zones in the world. Metropolitan France shares borders with Belgium and Luxembourg to the north, Germany to the north east, Switzerland to the east, Italy and Monaco to the south east, Andorra and Spain to the south, and a maritime border with the United Kingdom to the north west. Its metropolitan area extends from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean and from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea. Its overseas territories include French Guiana in South America, Saint Pierre and Miquelon in the North Atlantic, the French West Indies, and many islands in Oceania and the Indian Ocean. Its eighteen integral regions (five of which are overseas) span a combined area of 643,801 km2 (248,573 sq mi) and have a total population of over 68 million as of January 2023.[5][8] France is a unitary semi-presidential republic with its capital in Paris, the country\'s largest city and main cultural and commercial centre; other major urban areas include Marseille, Lyon, Toulouse, Lille, Bordeaux, Strasbourg, Nantes and Nice.

\n\n\t\tMetropolitan France was settled during the Iron Age by Celtic tribes known as Gauls before Rome annexed the area in 51 BC, leading to a distinct Gallo-Roman culture. In the Early Middle Ages, the Germanic Franks formed the Kingdom of Francia, which became the heartland of the Carolingian Empire. The Treaty of Verdun of 843 partitioned the empire, with West Francia evolving into the Kingdom of France. In the High Middle Ages, France was a powerful but decentralized feudal kingdom, but from the mid-14th to the mid-15th centuries, France was plunged into a dynastic conflict with England known as the Hundred Years\' War. In the 16th century, the French Renaissance saw culture flourish and a French colonial empire rise.[15] Internally, France was dominated by the conflict with the House of Habsburg and the French Wars of Religion between Catholics and Huguenots. France was successful in the Thirty Years\' War and further increased its influence during the reign of Louis XIV.[16]

\n\n\t\tThe French Revolution of 1789 overthrew the Ancien Régime and produced the Declaration of the Rights of Man, which expresses the nation\'s ideals to this day. France reached its political and military zenith in the early 19th century under Napoleon Bonaparte, subjugating part of continental Europe and establishing the First French Empire. The French Revolutionary and Napoleonic Wars significantly shaped the course of European history. The collapse of the empire initiated a period of relative decline, in which France endured a tumultuous succession of governments until the founding of the French Third Republic during the Franco-Prussian War in 1870. Subsequent decades saw a period of economic prosperity and cultural and scientific flourishing known as the Belle Époque. France was one of the major participants of World War I, from which it emerged victorious at great human and economic cost. It was among the Allied powers of World War II, but it surrendered and was occupied by the Axis in 1940. Following its liberation in 1944, the short-lived Fourth Republic was established and later dissolved in the course of the defeat in the Algerian War. The current Fifth Republic was formed in 1958 by Charles de Gaulle. Algeria and most French colonies became independent in the 1960s, with the majority retaining close economic and military ties with France.

\n\n\t\tFrance retains its centuries-long status as a global centre of art, science, and philosophy. It hosts the third-largest number of UNESCO World Heritage Sites and is the world\'s leading tourist destination, receiving over 89 million foreign visitors in 2018.[17] France is a developed country with a high nominal per capita income globally and its advanced economy ranks among the largest in the world. It is a great power in global affairs,[18] being one of the five permanent members of the United Nations Security Council and an official nuclear-weapon state. France is a founding and leading member of the European Union and the eurozone,[19] as well as a key member of the Group of Seven, North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), and Francophonie.

         </string>

    <string name="italy">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Rome \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Rome \n
        <b>National Language</b>\t: Italian \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 301,340 km^2 \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Euro \n\n

        \t\tItaly (Italian: Italia, Italian: [iˈtaːlja] ⓘ), officially the Italian Republic (Italian: Repubblica Italiana, Italian: [reˈpubblika itaˈljaːna]), is a country in Southern[14][15][16] and Western[17][a] Europe. Located in the middle of the Mediterranean Sea, it consists of a peninsula delimited by the Alps and surrounded by several islands.[18] Italy shares land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia and the enclaved microstates of Vatican City and San Marino. It has a territorial exclave in Switzerland (Campione) and an archipelago in the African Plate (Pelagie Islands). Italy covers an area of 301,340 km2 (116,350 sq mi),[3] with a population of nearly 60 million;[19] it is the tenth-largest country by land area in the European continent and the third-most populous member state of the European Union. Its capital and largest city is Rome.

\n\n\t\t The Italian peninsula was historically the native place and destination of numerous ancient peoples.[20] The Latin city of Rome in central Italy, founded as the Roman Kingdom, became a Republic that conquered the Mediterranean world and ruled it for centuries as an Empire.[21][22] With the spread of Christianity, Rome became the seat of the Catholic Church and of the Papacy. During the Early Middle Ages, Italy experienced the fall of the Western Roman Empire and inward migration from Germanic tribes. By the 11th century, Italian city-states and maritime republics expanded, bringing renewed prosperity through commerce and laying the groundwork for modern capitalism.[23][24] The Italian Renaissance flourished in Florence during the 15th and 16th centuries and spread to the rest of Europe. Italian explorers also discovered new routes to the Far East and the New World, helping to usher in the European Age of Discovery. However, centuries of rivalry and infighting between the Italian city-states among other factors left the peninsula divided into numerous states until the late modern period.[25][26] During the 17th and 18th centuries, the Italian economic and commercial importance significantly waned.[27]

\n\n\t\t After centuries of political and territorial divisions, Italy was almost entirely unified in 1861 following Wars of independence and the Expedition of the Thousand, establishing the Kingdom of Italy.[28] From the late 19th century to the early 20th century, Italy rapidly industrialised, mainly in the north, and acquired a colonial empire,[29] while the south remained largely impoverished and excluded from industrialisation, fuelling a large immigrant diaspora.[30] From 1915 to 1918, Italy took part in World War I on the side of the Entente and against the Central Powers. In 1922, following a period of crisis and turmoil, the Italian fascist dictatorship was established. During World War II, Italy was first part of the Axis until it surrendered to the Allied powers (1940–1943) and then, as part of its territory was occupied by Nazi Germany with fascist collaboration, a co-belligerent of the Allies during the Italian resistance and the liberation of Italy (1943–1945). Following the end of the war, the country replaced the monarchy with a republic via referendum and enjoyed a prolonged economic boom, becoming a major advanced economy.[31]

\n\n\t\t Italy has the eighth-largest nominal GDP in the world, the second-largest manufacturing industry in Europe (7th-largest in the world).[32] The country has a significant role in regional[33][34] and global[35][36] economic, military, cultural, and diplomatic affairs. Italy is a founding and leading member of the European Union, and it is in numerous international institutions including NATO, the G7, the Mediterranean Union, and the Latin Union. The source of many inventions and discoveries, the country is considered a cultural superpower and has long been a global centre of art, music, literature, cuisine, science and technology, and fashion.[37] It has the world\'s largest number of World Heritage Sites (58), and is the world\'s fifth-most visited country.


         </string>

    <string name="india">

        <b>Capital</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: New Delhi \n
        <b>Largest City</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Mumbai \n
        <b>Official Language</b>\t\t: Hindi \n
        <b>Total Area</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: 3,287,263 km^2 \n
        <b>Currency</b>\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t: Rupee \n\n

        \t\tItaly India, officially the Republic of India (ISO: Bhārat Gaṇarājya),[22] is a country in South Asia. It is the seventh-largest country by area; the most populous country as of June 2023;[23][24] and from the time of its independence in 1947, the world\'s most populous democracy.[25][26][27] Bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest, and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast, it shares land borders with Pakistan to the west;[j] China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the north; and Bangladesh and Myanmar to the east. In the Indian Ocean, India is in the vicinity of Sri Lanka and the Maldives; its Andaman and Nicobar Islands share a maritime border with Thailand, Myanmar, and Indonesia.

\n\n\t\t Modern humans arrived on the Indian subcontinent from Africa no later than 55,000 years ago.[28][29][30] Their long occupation, initially in varying forms of isolation as hunter-gatherers, has made the region highly diverse, second only to Africa in human genetic diversity.[31] Settled life emerged on the subcontinent in the western margins of the Indus river basin 9,000 years ago, evolving gradually into the Indus Valley Civilisation of the third millennium BCE.[32] By 1200 BCE, an archaic form of Sanskrit, an Indo-European language, had diffused into India from the northwest.[33][34] Its evidence today is found in the hymns of the Rigveda. Preserved by an oral tradition that was resolutely vigilant, the Rigveda records the dawning of Hinduism in India.[35] The Dravidian languages of India were supplanted in the northern and western regions.[36] By 400 BCE, stratification and exclusion by caste had emerged within Hinduism,[37] and Buddhism and Jainism had arisen, proclaiming social orders unlinked to heredity.[38] Early political consolidations gave rise to the loose-knit Maurya and Gupta Empires based in the Ganges Basin.[39] Their collective era was suffused with wide-ranging creativity,[40] but also marked by the declining status of women,[41] and the incorporation of untouchability into an organised system of belief.[k][42] In South India, the Middle kingdoms exported Dravidian-languages scripts and religious cultures to the kingdoms of Southeast Asia.[43]

\n\n\t\t In the early medieval era, Christianity, Islam, Judaism, and Zoroastrianism became established on India\'s southern and western coasts.[44] Muslim armies from Central Asia intermittently overran India\'s northern plains,[45] eventually founding the Delhi Sultanate, and drawing northern India into the cosmopolitan networks of medieval Islam.[46] In the 15th century, the Vijayanagara Empire created a long-lasting composite Hindu culture in south India.[47] In the Punjab, Sikhism emerged, rejecting institutionalised religion.[48] The Mughal Empire, in 1526, ushered in two centuries of relative peace,[49] leaving a legacy of luminous architecture.[l][50] Gradually expanding rule of the British East India Company followed, turning India into a colonial economy, but also consolidating its sovereignty.[51] British Crown rule began in 1858. The rights promised to Indians were granted slowly,[52][53] but technological changes were introduced, and modern ideas of education and the public life took root.[54] A pioneering and influential nationalist movement emerged, which was noted for nonviolent resistance and became the major factor in ending British rule.[55][56] In 1947 the British Indian Empire was partitioned into two independent dominions,[57][58][59][60] a Hindu-majority Dominion of India and a Muslim-majority Dominion of Pakistan, amid large-scale loss of life and an unprecedented migration.[61]

\n\n\t\t India has been a federal republic since 1950, governed through a democratic parliamentary system. It is a pluralistic, multilingual and multi-ethnic society. India\'s population grew from 361 million in 1951 to almost 1.4 billion in 2022.[62] During the same time, its nominal per capita income increased from US$64 annually to US$2,601, and its literacy rate from 16.6% to 74%. From being a comparatively destitute country in 1951,[63] India has become a fast-growing major economy and a hub for information technology services, with an expanding middle class.[64] India has a space programme with several planned or completed extraterrestrial missions. Indian movies, music, and spiritual teachings play an increasing role in global culture.[65] India has substantially reduced its rate of poverty, though at the cost of increasing economic inequality.[66] India is a nuclear-weapon state, which ranks high in military expenditure. It has disputes over Kashmir with its neighbours, Pakistan and China, unresolved since the mid-20th century.[67] Among the socio-economic challenges India faces are gender inequality, child malnutrition,[68] and rising levels of air pollution.[69] India\'s land is megadiverse, with four biodiversity hotspots.[70] Its forest cover comprises 21.7% of its area.[71] India\'s wildlife, which has traditionally been viewed with tolerance in India\'s culture,[72] is supported among these forests, and elsewhere, in protected habitats.



         </string>
</resources>